propertydirect.in 2012-12-03

# Privacy Policy - propertyDirect.in

The [propertydirect.in](http://www.propertydirect.in/) website is owned and operated by erpDirect(www.erpdirect.in). propertyDirect.in has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to our users privacy. We may use IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Website. Your IP address may be also used to gather broad demographic information. [propertydirect.in](http://www.propertydirect.in/) contains links to other websites and propertyDirect.in is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We may use a third party advertising company to display advertisement on [propertydirect.in](http://www.propertydirect.in/) (e.g. Google Adsense). These ads may contain cookies. While we may use cookies in other parts of our website, cookies received with banner adverts are collected by our advertising company, and we do not have access to this information. Certifiable information is collected from users and/or registered members of [propertydirect.in](http://www.propertydirect.in/) which includes, but may not be limited to: 

  * Email address 
  * Contact person name
  * User-created password
  * Mailing address
  * Pin code
  * Telephone number or other contact number

Except where you are explicitly informed, propertDirect.in do not sell, rent, share, trade or give away any of your personal information. [propertydirect.in](http://www.propertydirect.in/) may tie-up with partners to bring you various services. However, we will never share your personal information, without your explicitly permission. Still, we encourage you to review the privacy policy of the partner for questions about their use, any personally identifiable information that you may separately submit to such partner. If we change our privacy policy, we will prominently post a link to those changes on our Homepage so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you by way of an email. We will give you a choice as to whether or not we can use information in this different manner and act accordingly. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please write to us: Contact Us
